Women's Center Records UA156
Tufts Archival Research Center
Women's Center Records
1970 -- 2010
1964 -- 2020
Tufts Archival Research Center
Women's Center
UA156
22.63 Linear Feet 19 boxes
1 Volumes
1 Artifact(s)
32 Digital Object(s)
1 Web sites
7 Folder(s) 7 oversized folders
This collection contains the records of the Tufts University Women's Center.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by the Women's Center, 2011-2017.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into six series: Office files; Log books; Publications, pamphlets, and women's organizations; Web crawls; Unprocessed accessions; and 2017 accessions.
Biographical / Historical
Founded in December of 1972, the Women's Center was initially student-run and funded by the Tufts Community Union Senate. The Center spent its early years in the basements of Miller Hall and Curtis Hall, and the office changed locations several times before making its permanent home at 55 Talbot Avenue in 1988. In April, 1974 Gail Koplow was hired as Coordinator. In 1980, Peggy Barrett was hired as Health and Sexuality Counselor, and when the Center became an administrative office in 1985 Barrett was appointed part-time Director; she left this position in 2006. From 2006 Sue Gilbert served as Interim Director until 2008, when Steph Gauchel became Director. The Women's Center was instrumental in the development of numerous projects. In 1976 the Center established the Women's Community School to promote "non-traditional skills for women." Over the years, the Center offered events, orientation programs, counseling, and peer education programs aimed at raising awareness of women's and minority concerns and providing support for victims of sexual assault.
The Women's Center's mission statement follows: "The mission of the Tufts University Women's Center is to advance the personal growth and intellectual development of all students, and especially women, particularly on issues related to women and gender. We are committed to fostering student leadership and helping students identify and understand societal structures that relate to issues of power, privilege, and oppression as well as providing resources to graduate students, faculty and staff, alumni, and parents. In this pursuit, the center offers programming, advising, information, and resources about women, men, and gender that are informed by other aspects of identity such as race and ethnicity, sexual orientation, gender identity and expression, and socioeconomic class."
Related Materials
Women's Studies Program Records, 1969-2011. Tufts University. Digital Collections and Archives. Medford, MA.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the records of the Tufts University Women's Center, including correspondence, office files, log books, newsletters, and slides and photographs.
There are also programming materials, presentations, event posters, and videotapes of events and speakers at the Women's Center, as well as the web crawls documenting the Women's Center's presence on the web. The collection also contains non-Tufts publications concerning the women's movement and women's issues more generally.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list. This collection may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
Student Affairs and Services; Student life; Student Activities -- Student Government, Clubs, and Organizations; Student activism; Health and Safety
- Office files, 1972 -- 2007; UA156.001; 9.4 Linear Feet; 16 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains subject files relating to conference and workshop planning, staff training, programming, and counseling, as well as some posters, artifacts, correspondence and photographs. The files date from 1972 to 2006 and were created by several different staff members and student assistants. Materials from the 1970s chart the creation and early development of the Women's Center, when it was run first by a student group, followed in 1974 by Coordinator Gail Koplow. Most records dating from 1980 - 2006 are from Peggy Barrett, Health and Sexuality Counselor and Director of the Center. From 1985 on Peggy Barrett also worked half-time as administrator for the Women's Studies program, and therefore some records from her work in that position are interspersed among the files of this series. Four conferences hosted by Tufts and coordinated in part by the Women's Center are well documented in this series: Women of Many Visions (1985), Changing Our Minds (1989), NEWSA (New England Women's Studies Association) Conference (1992), and Women and Representation in the Media (1994). In 1999 the Women's Center received the first of four two-year grants of $1.3 million from the Department of Justice. The grant application and the Campus Violence Prevention Project (CVPP) funded by the grant are documented in this series. The CVPP sponsored a number of initiatives aimed at raising awareness of rape and sexual assault and providing counseling for victims. These initiatives included culturally-specific workshops oriented towards Latino and LGBT communities, publication of brochures, staff education, peer education, and SSARA (Student Sexual Assault Response Assistance), a telephone hotline run by students that offered rapid response counseling services starting in 2001.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged as received.
  Conditions Governing Access
  75 years from the date of creation. Open for research.
  - [Ledger, 1 of 3], 1973 -- 1974; UA156.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
    75 years from the date of creation.
  - [Ledger, 2 of 3], 1973 -- 1974; UA156.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
    Open for research.
  - [Ledger, 3 of 3], 1973 -- 1974; UA156.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Umbrella log, 1980 -- 1983; UA156.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Laura Driscoll work study fall, 1980; UA156.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - [Pay steps], 1980; UA156.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Employees, 1979; UA156.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
    Back of folder reads: exercise classes for staff, union organizing
  - [Internship], 1980; UA156.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Independent study info, internships at Women's Centers, 1977 -- 1980; UA156.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - [New England Women's Studies Association meeting attendance list], 1984; UA156.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1988 -- 1989; UA156.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1985; UA156.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - [Contraception education fliers], 1980; UA156.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - [Rape Collective contact list], 1975; UA156.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - [Vouchers and employment form], 1981 -- 1982; UA156.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - [Support group leadership training], 1980; UA156.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Work study student, 1980 -- 1981; UA156.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Ditto masters, 1980; UA156.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Newspaper clippings fall, 1987; UA156.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Women at Tufts articles, 1977 -- 1978; UA156.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
    Also includes financial material and program descriptions.
  - [Budget proposal, organization evaluation, and other material], 1981; UA156.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Relationships workshop, 1981; UA156.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - [Sexuality counseling], 1976 -- 1978; UA156.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Abortion Action Coalition, 1972; UA156.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - Intercultural women's group, 1977; UA156.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Women's Center advisory board, 1979; UA156.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - [Women's Center Network Conference flier], 1980; UA156.001.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - Sexuality course, 1980; UA156.001.001.00028 (Box 1)
  - [Newspaper clippings], 1984; UA156.001.001.00029 (Box 1)
  - [Film possibilities], 1980; UA156.001.001.00030 (Box 1)
  - Old Women's Center events, 1976 -- 1985; UA156.001.001.00031 (Box 1)
  - Herstory, 1976 -- 1978; UA156.001.001.00032 (Box 1)
    Includes materials relating to the Women's Community School.
  - Tufts Women's Center herstory, 1973; UA156.001.001.00033 (Box 1)
  - Health and sexuality counselor, 1977 -- 1980; UA156.001.001.00034 (Box 1)
  - [Women's health services], 1980; UA156.001.001.00035 (Box 1)
  - [Events], 1975 -- 1990; UA156.001.001.00036 (Box 1)
  - [WORC Newsletter], 1980; UA156.001.001.00037 (Box 1)
  - [Student survey], 1979 -- 1980; UA156.001.001.00038 (Box 1)
  - [Peer education] manual - 1st page, 1998; UA156.001.001.00039 (Box 1)
  - [Peer education] facilitation chapter, 1998; UA156.001.001.00040 (Box 1)
  - [Peer education] preparing to lead, 1998; UA156.001.001.00041 (Box 1)
  - Peer education - rape/sexual assault - workshop ideas, 1997 -- 1998; UA156.001.001.00042 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin boards, 1996 -- 1999; UA156.001.001.00043 (Box 1)
  - THINK materials, 1989 -- 1990; UA156.001.001.00044 (Box 1)
  - THINK, 1990 -- 1992; UA156.001.001.00045 (Box 1)
  - [THINK], 1990; UA156.001.001.00046 (Box 1)
  - THINK - table tents, 1990; UA156.001.001.00047 (Box 1)
  - THINK - posters I, 1990; UA156.001.001.00048 (Box 1)
    Folder also reads: General postering, newspaper ads
  - THINK - posters II, 1990; UA156.001.001.00049 (Box 1)
    Folder also reads: Specific school events, holidays/exams, meeting announcements. Original folder is empty.
  - THINK - communications workshop info, 1990; UA156.001.001.00050 (Box 1)
  - THINK, 1991; UA156.001.001.00051 (Box 1)
  - THINK - resources I, 1992; UA156.001.001.00052 (Box 1)
    Folder also reads: pamphlets, fact/rape stat. sheets, surveys/questionnaires.
  - THINK - resources II, 1992; UA156.001.001.00053 (Box 1)
    Folder also reads: resources lists, bibliographies, order forms.
  - THINK - resources III, 1992; UA156.001.001.00054 (Box 1)
    Folder also reads: programs from other schools - Mid-Missouri Men's Resource Group, COAR - Campus Organized Against Rape State U. New York, DARE - Date Acquaintance Rape Ed.
  - [Postcards], 1997; UA156.001.001.00055 (Box 1)
  - Women's Center fliers, 1996; UA156.001.001.00056 (Box 1)
  - Pictures [1 of 8], 1996; UA156.001.001.00057 (Box 1)
    - Tufts students at a women's festival, 1996-10-18; UA156.001.001.00057.00001 (Box 1)
      Students; Student activities; Congresses and conventions; Festivals; Women's rights; photographic print; Women's Center; Tufts University
  - Pictures [2 of 8], 1997; UA156.001.001.00058 (Box 1)
    - Woman sitting on a couch in the Women's Center, 1997; UA156.001.001.00058.00001 (Box 1)
      photographic print; Women's Center; Tufts University
    - Women students holding signs, 1997; UA156.001.001.00058.00002 (Box 1)
      Students; photographic print; Women's Center; Tufts University
    - 'The Tufts Women', 1997; UA156.001.001.00058.00003 (Box 1)
      Students; Women college students; photographic print; Women's Center; Tufts University
  - Pictures [3 of 8], 1981; UA156.001.001.00059 (Box 1)
    - Group shot of women dancing, 1981; UA156.001.001.00059.00001 (Box 1)
      photographic print; Barrett, Peggy; Women's Center; Tufts University
  - Pictures [4 of 8], 1995; UA156.001.001.00060 (Box 1)
  - Pictures [5 of 8], 1988; UA156.001.001.00061 (Box 1)
    - Peggy Barrett, Women's Center Director, 1988; UA156.001.001.00061.00001 (Box 1)
    - Women students sitting on a couch, 1988; UA156.001.001.00061.00002 (Box 1)
    - Two women students sitting on a couch, 1988; UA156.001.001.00061.00003 (Box 1)
  - Pictures [6 of 8], 1986; UA156.001.001.00062 (Box 1)
    Also includes postcards.
    - Meeting of women students, 1986; UA156.001.001.00062.00001 (Box 1)
      Women college students; Students; Student activities; photographic print; Women's Center; Tufts University
    - Meeting of women students, 1986; UA156.001.001.00062.00002 (Box 1)
      Women college students; Students; Student activities; photographic print; Barrett, Peggy; Women's Center; Tufts University
    - Group shot of women, 1986; UA156.001.001.00062.00003 (Box 1)
    - Group shot of women flexing their muscles!, 1986; UA156.001.001.00062.00004 (Box 1)
  - Pictures [7 of 8], 1995; UA156.001.001.00063 (Box 1)
    Jane Doe Walk
    - Jane Doe Walk, 1995; UA156.001.001.00063.00001 (Box 1)
      Students; Student activities; Women college students; photographic print; Barrett, Peggy; Women's Center; Tufts University
    - Tufts Muslim Women Against Domestic Violence, 1995; UA156.001.001.00063.00002 (Box 1)
      Students; Student activities; Women college students; Muslim women; photographic print; Women's Center; Tufts University
  - Pictures [8 of 8], 1996 -- 1997; UA156.001.001.00064 (Box 1)
    Contains anti-sweat shop brochures and comics.
  - [Calendar], 1998; UA156.001.001.00065 (Box 1)
  - [Correspondence], 1979 -- 1998; UA156.001.001.00066 (Box 1)
  - [Printed material], 1977 -- 1997; UA156.001.001.00067 (Box 1)
  - [Healthy and abusive relationships], 1998; UA156.001.001.00068 (Box 1)
  - Healthy and abusive [relationships] - evaluations, 1996 -- 1997; UA156.001.001.00069 (Box 1)
  - [Body Image - Collection of Poems], 1998; UA156.001.001.00070 (Box 1)
  - Scheherazade, 2000; UA156.001.001.00071 (Box 1)
  - Spring programs, 1999 -- 2000; UA156.001.001.00072 (Box 1)
  - Rebecca Walker, 2000; UA156.001.001.00073 (Box 1)
  - Women's Week ideas, 1993 -- 1997; UA156.001.001.00074 (Box 1)
  - [Brochures, 1 of 2], 1998 -- 1999; UA156.001.001.00075 (Box 1)
  - [Brochures, 2 of 2], 1995 -- 1999; UA156.001.001.00076 (Box 1)
  - Health, 1999; UA156.001.001.00077 (Box 1)
  - SuWu, 2000; UA156.001.001.00078 (Box 1)
  - College women's centers, 1998; UA156.001.001.00079 (Box 1)
  - Getting help, 1999; UA156.001.001.00080 (Box 1)
  - Violence, 1999; UA156.001.001.00081 (Box 1)
  - Childcare WEJ, 1994; UA156.001.001.00082 (Box 1)
    Childcare service sponsored by Women for Economic Justice.
  - [Women and Representation in Mass Media conference] evaluations, 1994; UA156.001.001.00083 (Box 1)
  - [Women and Representation in Mass Media conference logistics], 1994; UA156.001.001.00084 (Box 1)
    Original title reads: 94 conf. logistics
  - [Women and Representation in Mass Media conference - publicity], 1994; UA156.001.001.00085 (Box 1)
    Original title reads: 94 conf - publicity
  - [Women and Representation in Mass Media conference - planning committee], 1994; UA156.001.001.00086 (Box 1)
    Original title reads: Conf 94 - planning committee.
  - [Women and Representation in Mass Media conference - speaker information], 1994; UA156.001.001.00087 (Box 1)
    Original title reads: Conf 94 - speaker info
  - [Women and Representation in Mass Media conference - brochures], 1994; UA156.001.001.00088 (Box 1)
    Original title reads: Conf 94 - brochures
  - NEWSA, 1990; UA156.001.001.00089 (Box 1)
  - [Conference information], 1985 -- 1990; UA156.001.001.00090 (Box 1)
  - Asian American Women Writers [conference], 1990; UA156.001.001.00091 (Box 1)
  - [NEWSA conference - meeting notes], 1992; UA156.001.001.00092 (Box 1)
    Original title reads: 1992 conf. meeting notes.
  - [NEWSA conference - planning committee], 1991; UA156.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
    Original title reads: 1992 conf. - planning committee.
  - [NEWSA conference] logistics, 1990 -- 1992; UA156.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - [Boston guide], 1991; UA156.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
    Original title reads: Registration packets
  - [NEWSA conference - call for proposals], 1991; UA156.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
    Original title reads: 1992 conf. call for proposals.
  - [NEWSA conference - announcement], 1992; UA156.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
    Original title reads: 1992 conf. announcement.
  - [NEWSA conference - advertise call], 1991 -- 1992; UA156.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
    Original title reads: 1992 conf. advertise call and conference.
  - [NEWSA conference] disability information, 1992; UA156.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - [NEWSA conference - evaluation], 1992; UA156.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
    Original title reads: 1992 conf. evaluation.
  - [NEWSA conference - keynote panel], 1991 -- 1992; UA156.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
    Original title reads: 1992 conf. - keynote panel.
  - [NEWSA conference] displays, 1992; UA156.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - [NEWSA conference - rejected proposals], 1991; UA156.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
    Original title reads: 1992 conf. - rejected proposals.
  - [NEWSA conference - opening remarks], 1992; UA156.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
    Original title reads: 1992 conf. opening remarks.
  - [NEWSA conference information], 1991 -- 1992; UA156.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
    Original title reads: 1992 conf. NEWSA info.
  - [NEWSA conference - forming committee], 1990 -- 1991; UA156.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
    Original title reads: 1992 conf forming committee.
  - [NEWSA conference information], 1991; UA156.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
    Original title reads: 1992 conf. NWSA info.
  - [NEWSA conference - mailing lists], 1991; UA156.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
    Original title reads: Mailing lists used for 1992 conf.
  - [Conference] calendar listings, 1987 -- 1992; UA156.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - American studies lists, 1990; UA156.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - [NEWSA conference] summary and evaluations, 1992; UA156.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - [NEWSA conference - follow-up], 1992; UA156.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
    Original title reads: 1992 conf. follow-up.
  - [NEWSA conference - registration], 1992; UA156.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
    Original title reads: 1992 conf. - registration.
  - [NEWSA conference] workshops, 1991 -- 1992; UA156.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
  - [NEWSA conference] workshop development, 1991; UA156.001.002.00023 (Box 2)
  - [NEWSA workshop] 1 - moving away from violence - envisioning a new power struggle, 1991; UA156.001.002.00024 (Box 2)
  - [NEWSA workshop] 2 - mental, physical, and emotional violence, 1991; UA156.001.002.00025 (Box 2)
  - [NEWSA workshop] 3 - women's health - personal and political, 1991; UA156.001.002.00026 (Box 2)
  - [NEWSA workshop] 4 - women surviving, 1991; UA156.001.002.00027 (Box 2)
  - [NEWSA workshop] 5 - making connections - breaking the isolations of the workplace, 1991 -- 1992; UA156.001.002.00028 (Box 2)
  - [NEWSA workshop] 6 - becoming multicultural and multiracial, 1991; UA156.001.002.00029 (Box 2)
  - [NEWSA workshop] 7 - women organizing on campus I, 1991; UA156.001.002.00030 (Box 2)
  - [NEWSA workshop] 8 - women organizing on campus II, 1991; UA156.001.002.00031 (Box 2)
  - [NEWSA workshop] 9 - knowledge, 1991; UA156.001.002.00032 (Box 2)
  - [NEWSA workshop] 10 - cultural activism, 1991; UA156.001.002.00033 (Box 2)
  - [NEWSA workshop] 11 - women, media, and stereotypes, 1991; UA156.001.002.00034 (Box 2)
  - [NEWSA workshop] 12 - organizing around family, 1991; UA156.001.002.00035 (Box 2)
  - [NEWSA workshop] 13 - violence and children, 1991; UA156.001.002.00036 (Box 2)
  - [NEWSA workshop] 14 - women building international solidarity, 1991 -- 1992; UA156.001.002.00037 (Box 2)
  - [NEWSA workshop] 15 - identity formation, 1991; UA156.001.002.00038 (Box 2)
  - [NEWSA workshop] 16 - making the system work for us I, 1991; UA156.001.002.00039 (Box 2)
  - [NEWSA workshop] 17 - making the system work for us II, 1991; UA156.001.002.00040 (Box 2)
  - [NEWSA workshop] 18 - women in recovery, 1991; UA156.001.002.00041 (Box 2)
  - [NEWSA workshop] 20 - women and work, 1991; UA156.001.002.00042 (Box 2)
  - Women of Many Visions [conference] - notes for Susan O., 1987; UA156.001.002.00043 (Box 2)
  - [Changing Our Minds conference] - extra copies, 1989; UA156.001.002.00044 (Box 2)
    Original title reads: Conf 89 - extra copies.
  - [Women of Many Visions] conference - fall, 1987; UA156.001.002.00045 (Box 2)
  - [Women of Many Visions conference] - mother / daughter panel, 1987; UA156.001.002.00046 (Box 2)
  - [Changing Our Minds conference - correspondence], 1990; UA156.001.002.00047 (Box 2)
  - [Changing Our Minds conference] - Shirley Hune, 1989; UA156.001.002.00048 (Box 2)
  - [Changing Our Minds] conference evaluation, 1989; UA156.001.002.00049 (Box 2)
  - [Changing Our Minds] conference registration curriculum, 1989; UA156.001.002.00050 (Box 2)
  - [Changing Our Minds] conference, fall, 1989; UA156.001.002.00051 (Box 2)
  - [Changing Our Minds] conference money, 1989; UA156.001.002.00052 (Box 2)
  - [Changing Our Minds conference] - state of the disciplines, 1989; UA156.001.002.00053 (Box 2)
  - [Women of Many Visions conference] - keynote information, 1987; UA156.001.002.00054 (Box 2)
  - [Women of Many Visions] conference money, 1987; UA156.001.002.00055 (Box 2)
  - [Women of Many Visions conference - fliers and registration sheets], 1987; UA156.001.002.00056 (Box 2)
  - [Women of Many Visions conference] - copies of history, 1987; UA156.001.002.00057 (Box 2)
  - Women of Many Visions [conference] evaluations, 1987; UA156.001.002.00058 (Box 2)
  - Women of Many Visions [conference] follow-up, 1987; UA156.001.002.00059 (Box 2)
  - [Women of Many Visions conference] - attendance, 1987; UA156.001.002.00060 (Box 2)
  - Western Feminism and Third World Women conference, 1985; UA156.001.002.00061 (Box 2)
  - [Women of Many Visions conference poster], 1987; UA156.001.002.00062 (Box 2)
  - [Changing Our Minds conference - correspondence], 1989; UA156.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Guest lists, 1986; UA156.001.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - Development, 1986; UA156.001.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - [Women's studies programs] - general information, 1985 -- 1986; UA156.001.003.00004 (Box 3)
    Original title reads: W.S./W.P. general info.
  - [Women's studies] library journals, 1987; UA156.001.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - Costa Rica, 1988; UA156.001.003.00006 (Box 3)
    Booklet in Spanish, titled: "Centro Interdisciplinario de Estudios de la Mujer"
  - Press lists, 1986; UA156.001.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - Media contacts, 1986; UA156.001.003.00008 (Box 3)
  - ACES report, 1989 -- 1990; UA156.001.003.00009 (Box 3)
  - Wessell library, 1989; UA156.001.003.00010 (Box 3)
  - [Women's studies] - Boston area, 1986 -- 1990; UA156.001.003.00011 (Box 3)
  - I Am Your Sister, 1990; UA156.001.003.00012 (Box 3)
  - Yale conference, 1991, UA156.001.003.00013 (Box 3)
  - Women's studies - general, 1988 -- 1989; UA156.001.003.00014 (Box 3)
  - Speaker ideas, 1993 -- 1998; UA156.001.003.00015 (Box 3)
  - ACES report on women in higher education 1987, UA156.001.003.00016 (Box 3)
  - Black Women in Academia, 1989; UA156.001.003.00017 (Box 3)
    Contains an article by Yolanda T. Moses.
  - Women faculty issues, 1992; UA156.001.003.00018 (Box 3)
    Contains an article "Success and Survival Strategies for Women Faculty Members" by Bernice Resnick Sandler.
  - Tenure and women, 1989; UA156.001.003.00019 (Box 3)
  - [Women's studies programs], 1989 -- 1991; UA156.001.003.00020 (Box 3)
  - [Internships], 1996; UA156.001.003.00021 (Box 3)
    Original title reads: 'Abortion - gen. info', but this does not reflect the actual contents of the folder.
  - Questionnaires - Katie Koestner [1 of 3] sp, 1998; UA156.001.003.00022 (Box 3)
  - Questionnaires - Katie Koestner [2 of 3], 1998; UA156.001.003.00023 (Box 3)
  - Questionnaires - Katie Koestner [3 of 3], 1998; UA156.001.003.00024 (Box 3)
  - Jane Doe, 1998; UA156.001.003.00025 (Box 3)
  - Jane Doe, 1992 -- 1998; UA156.001.003.00026 (Box 3)
  - Jane Doe walk, 1995 -- 1998; UA156.001.003.00027 (Box 3)
  - [Bitch magazine], 2001; UA156.001.003.00028 (Box 3)
  - [Campus Violence Prevention Project, 1 of 2], 2000 -- 2001; UA156.001.003.00029 (Box 3)
  - [Campus Violence Prevention Project, 2 of 2], 2000; UA156.001.003.00030 (Box 3)
  - [The Children We Sacrifice workshop], 2001 -- 2002; UA156.001.003.00031 (Box 3)
  - Grant copies, 1999; UA156.001.003.00032 (Box 3)
  - [Boston Area Rape Crisis Center], 1999 -- 2000; UA156.001.003.00033 (Box 3)
  - [Boston Area Rape Crisis Center], 2000; UA156.001.003.00034 (Box 3)
  - [Campus violence articles], 2000; UA156.001.003.00035 (Box 3)
  - [Domestic violence and Latino communities], 2000; UA156.001.003.00036 (Box 3)